(651) 373-5945 🤳

# Ryan **Harley**

rharley.dev@gmail.com ≥

LinkedIn in

Github 🖸

Website •

### **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER**

I am a full-stack developer specializing in JavaScript and Nodejs. My experience has provided me with a variety of web development knowledge and practical skills – primarily HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Nodejs, MongoDB, React, and React Native. I am passionate about coding and the amazing things I can create with code. I would love to join a team where I can not only utilize my existing skills, but also expand on them.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Audio Engineer**

Marriage Builders Radio: Apr 2018 - Present

Edit podcasts for the company's public archives and to broadcast to radio stations.
Continually find and develop techniques to improve audio quality.

## **General Manager**

Kirkwood Crates LLC: Aug 2018 - Mar 2020

- Responsible for finding new clients and maintaining client relations. Meet with clients to verify healthy relationship, address any concerns, and talk about future projects and developments within both companies.
- Schedule daily and weekly goals for company employees. Help on the operations floor by cutting lumber, building, and assembling wooden crates for on- time deliveries.
- In charge of finances and financial decisions, including buying lumber and supplies, create financial reports, manage documentation of business transactions, and more.

#### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web and Mobile App Developer | NUCAMP 2020

**Bachelors in Business Administration | Metropolitan State University** 2014 – 2017

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5	CSS3	JavaScript ES6+	React
NodeJS	MongoDB	Express	Bootstrap
RESTful API	NPM	Git	Agile Methods